Finding Aid for Bay View Club (Fenton, Mich.) minutes, 1897-1970
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Bay View Club (Fenton, Mich.) minutes 1897-1970
Bay View Club (Fenton, Mich.).
2 linear feet
851212 Bk.w 2
Women's social and reading society. Minutes, programs, membership lists, and miscellaneous papers read before the club.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The records came to the library from Mrs. Raymond Hyde (donor no. 4089 ).
No further additions to the records are expected.
The record group is open to research.
The Bay View Club was originally called the Bay View Reading Circle of Fenton. The organization is a women's social and literary club.
The record group consists almost entirely of minutes of the meetings of the organization dating from 1897 to 1970. There are, in addition, a scattering of programs, membership lists, and papers read at club meetings.
Subjects:
Arts--Michigan--Fenton--Societies, etc.; Bay View Reading Circle of Fenton (Mich.); Fenton (Mich.); Genesee County (Mich.); Women--Michigan--Fenton--Societies and clubs.; Group reading--Michigan--Fenton.
- Minutes of meetings
  - 1897-1910 and 1917-1957, 17 volumes (Box 1)
  - 1957-1958 (Box 2)
  - 1958-1959 (Box 2)
  - 1959-1960 (Box 2)
  - 1960-1962 (Box 2)
  - 1962-1964 (Box 2)
  - 1964-1965 (Box 2)
  - 1968-1970 (Box 2)
- Other materials
  - Miscellaneous programs, membership lists, and papers (Box 2)